是时候迎接另一个激动人心的编码挑战了
Time for another exciting coding challenge
这样您就可以继续练习新的 HTML 技能。
so that you can keep practicing your new HTML skills.
在这个中，我希望你构建这个组件
And in this one, I want you to build this component
对于这款匡威全明星鞋。
for this Converse All Star shoe.
我在这里说组件
And I'm saying component here
因为我想让你想象这里的内容
because I want you to imagine this content here
在电子商务商店之类的环境中。
in the context of something like an e-commerce store.
所以想象一下我们有一家鞋店
So imagine that we have a shoe store
并且有多双鞋，每一双，
and there are multiple shoes and for each of them,
然后有像这个小组件
there is then like this small component
有了这个描述。
with this description.
所以像价格这样的东西，
So stuff like the price,
一个简短的描述，一个链接
a short description, a link
然后是这里的一些产品细节。
and then some product details here.
现在，我正在构建这个组件，
Now, I am building this component,
所以我正在写这个 HTML
so I'm writing this HTML
在一个名为 codepen.io 的特殊编码平台上。
on a special coding platform called codepen.io.
所以这是一个在线的地方
So this is a place online
我们基本上可以在其中编写代码
where we can basically write our code
然后它会自动执行代码
and it will then automatically execute the code
并渲染它，它也很容易
and render it and it makes it also easy
分享该代码。
to share that code.
现在，当然，您不需要使用 CodePen
Now, of course, you don't need to use CodePen
为了完成这个挑战。
in order to complete this challenge.
你可以去你的代码编辑器
You can just go to your code editor
例如，在此处添加一个全新的 HTML 文件
and for example, add a brand new HTML file here
然后在那里构建所有代码。
and then build all the code in there.
我在视频中不这样做的原因
The reason why I'm not doing that here in the video
是因为我们实际上要建造
is because we're actually gonna build
稍后在这个挑战上。
on this challenge later.
所以我们将继续开发这个非常小的项目
So we will keep developing this very small project
在接下来的几节中
over the next few sections
然后会造成混乱
and that will then create a mess
不同的文件和许多不同的代码。
of different files and a lot of different code.
但当然，因为你是自己做的，
But of course, because you're doing it on your own,
在自己的电脑上，
on your own computer,
对你来说更容易
it's easier for you
所以你可以，就像我说的，
and so you can just, as I said,
如果需要，创建一个新的 HTML 文件并在此处执行。
if you want, create a new HTML file and do it here.
但另一方面，
But on the other hand,
我认为它也很有帮助和有用
I think it's also helpful and useful
让你了解一下codepen.io
for you to learn a little bit about codepen.io
并在那里创造挑战。
and create the challenge there.
所以让我给你
So let me just give you
CodePen 的快速演示。
a very quick demonstration of CodePen.
所以我会说谷歌 CodePen
So just google CodePen I would say
或者你可以去 codepen.io。
or you can go to codepen.io.
然后你所要做的就是点击这里
And then all you have to is to click here
关于开始编码。
on Start Coding.
现在，也许在未来，
Now, maybe in the future,
CodePen 发生了一些变化，
something has changed about CodePen,
所以关于这个界面
so about this interface
但您将始终能够创建一个新的 CodePen
but you will always be able to create a new CodePen
只需访问 codepen.io/pen。
simply by going to codepen.io/pen.
所以就像这样。
So just like this.
所以这里我们基本上有一个面板
So here we basically have a panel
我们可以在其中编写 HTML、CSS
where we can write HTML, CSS
如果我们愿意，还有 JavaScript。
and JavaScript if we want.
或者我们也可以折叠这些面板
Or we can also just collapse these panels
如果我们不需要它们，
if we don't need them,
现在就是这种情况。
which is the case right now.
所以我们可以编写我们的 HTML。
And so we can write our HTML.
让我们只写一个 h1 元素。
00:02:54,85​​0 --> 00:02:56,803
你好，世界，例如。
Let's just write an h1 element.
Hello, World, for example.
你看我们有
And you see that here we have
再次手动关闭元素。
to again manually close the element.
但不管怎样，你会看到一段时间后，
But anyway, you see that after some time,
然后它将结果呈现在这里。
It then renders the result down here.
所以基本上在这个结果面板中。
So in this results panel basically.
您还可以更改 CodePen 的名称。
You can also change the name of your CodePen.
所以让我们说挑战＃2，
So let's say Challenge #2,
这是 thi 的名字的讲座。
which is the name of this lecture.
好的，然后你也可以保存它。
Okay, and then you can also save it.
现在，要保存它，您必须创建一个免费帐户
Now, to save it, you will have to create a free account
但我会说这样做实际上是值得的。
but I would say that it's actually worthwhile to do so.
但当然，它是可选的，你不是被迫的
But of course, it's optional and you're not forced
在此处创建一个新帐户
to create a new account here
但如果你这样做，那实际上很有帮助
but if you do, that is actually very helpful
因为那样你会得到一个特殊的 URL
because then you will get a special URL
每个 CodePen
for each CodePen
然后你就可以和其他人分享那个 CodePen。
and then you can share that CodePen with others.
所以如果你想创建一个简单的例子，
So if you want to just like create a quick example,
快速演示
a quick demo of something
向某人展示，
to show it to someone,
那么你就可以来 CodePen，
then you can just come to CodePen,
在这里创建它
create it right here
然后从这里复制、粘贴 URL
and then copy, paste the URL from here
一旦你保存了它
once you have saved it
顺便说一下，
and by the way,
我刚才描述的其实也是最好的方法
what I just described is actually also the best way
在 Udemy 的问答部分共享代码
of sharing code in the Q&amp;A section on Udemy
以防您遇到任何问题。
in case you run into any problems.
好的？
Okay?
再说一次，这可能是个好主意
So again, it would probably be a good idea
在此处创建帐户
to create an account here
因为它只是有用
because it's just useful
很多很多程序员都使用 CodePen。
and many, many programmers use CodePen.
这是一个非常流行的工具。
It's a very popular tool.
但无论如何，现在回到挑战，
But anyway, going back now to the challenge,
让我给你一些提示。
let me give you a couple of hints.
好的，这就是结果的样子
Okay, so this is what the result looks like
我想让你建造
that I want you to build
但为了帮助你一点，
but to help you a little bit,
我实际上需要在这里更改一些代码。
I will actually need to change here a bit of the code.
所以在更改视图中，
So here in Change View,
我们现在可以切换到编辑器视图，
we can now switch to the editor view,
然后看起来就像我之前向您展示的一样。
which will then look just like what I showed you before.
好的，现在我们把编辑放在首位
All right, so now we have the editors here on top
然后结果下来。
and then the result down here.
所以有些事情我需要解释
So there are some things I need to explain
在你开始之前。
before you can get started.
所以首先，我想让你把所有的
So first of all, I want you to wrap all
文章元素内的此内容。
of this content inside an article element.
记住我提到的
And remember how I mentioned
文章元素不能只被使用
that an article element cannot only be used
对于诸如书面博客文章之类的内容
for something like a written blog post article
但也适合真正的物理文章
but also for like really a physical article
所以像这样的鞋子就是一个很好的例子。
and so a shoe like this is a perfect example for that.
所以这是一篇文章
So this is an article
再一次，回到这个例子
and again, coming back to the example
拥有像一个电子商务商店，
of having like an e-commerce store,
那么每双鞋都是不同的文章
then each shoe would be a different article
所以你会有一个文章元素
and so you would have one article element
每双鞋，对吧？
for each of the shoes, right?
然后在这里，有一个我们从未使用过的元素，
Then down here, there's an element that we have never used,
这是这个可点击的按钮。
which is this clickable button.
所以在这里，
And so down here,
您会看到这只是按钮元素。
you see that this is simply the button element.
所以你可以继续使用它。
And so you can just go ahead and use that.
最后，还有别的东西，
And then finally, there's something else,
这里是这个符号，所以这里是这个箭头。
which is this symbol here, so this arrow here.
现在，记得回到我们的项目中，
Now, remember how back in our project,
所以在这里，我在这里提到了这个符号，
so here, I mentioned that this symbol right here,
这个版权符号是一个 HTML 实体，对吧？
this copyright symbol is an HTML entity, right?
记住这一点，所以这个箭头在这里
Remember that, and so this arrow here
只是另一个 HTML 实体。
is just another HTML entity.
而且我当时也提过
And I also mentioned back then
有一个非常方便的清单
that there is a very handy list
在我的资源页面上，就是这个。
on my resources page, which is this one.
现在，如果你以后看这个，
Now, if you're watching this in the future,
那么这个页面可能看起来很不一样
then this page probably looks quite different
但现在，这就是我所拥有的
but for now, this is what I have
以及我的意思的 HTML 实体引用，
and the HTML entity reference that I meant,
所以我前面提到的就是这个。
so that I mentioned earlier is this one.
所以让我们实际打开它
So let's just open it up actually
然后有很多东西可以使用。
and then there is a lot of stuff that you can use.
所以所有这些不同的符号
So all of these different symbols
例如，这里是复制符号
and here, for example, is the copy symbol
我们之前在 VS Code 中使用过的。
that we used before in VS Code.
现在，这是一个巨大的清单
Now, this is a huge list
我只是要使用一个命令
and I'm just going to use a Command
或 Control + F 在页面上搜索箭头
or Control + F to search on the page for arrows
现在我们开始。
and here we go.
所以这里有所有这些不同的箭头
So there are all these different arrows here
我用的是这个。
and the one that I used is this.
所以要插入这个箭头
So to insert this arrow
到您自己的 HTML 代码中，
into your own HTML code,
您所要做的就是编写这个 HTML 实体。
all you have to do is to write this HTML entity.
好的？
Okay?
是的，我会离开这个。
And yeah, I will leave this.
哦，好吧，实际上，我们不再需要它了。
Oh, well, actually, we don't need it anymore.
对。
Right.
哦，还有一件事，
Oh, and just one more thing,
这是图像。
which is the image.
所以你不能真正将图像上传到 CodePen
So you cannot really upload images to CodePen
除非您有付费帐户
unless you have a paid account
但我认为这没有意义。
but that doesn't make sense I think.
所以我实际上为你上传了图片
And so I actually uploaded the image for you
到这个网址。
onto this URL.
所以你看到这实际上是另一种方式
So you see that this is actually another way
包括图像。
of including images.
所以本质上，一个即将到来的图像
So essentially, an image that is coming
从某个网址。
from a certain URL.
所以相比之下，就在这里，
So in contrast, right here,
当我们之前编写代码时，
when we wrote our code before,
那么源始终是图像
then the source was always an image
在我们自己的电脑上。
on our own computer.
所以在这种情况下，在图像文件夹中
So in this case, in the image folder
然后是这个图像名称。
and then this image name.
如果你在自己的电脑上构建这个挑战，
And if you're building this challenge on your own computer,
那么你可以在这里使用这个挑战图像。
then you can just use this challenge image here.
所以它是完全一样的。
So it's exactly the same.
好的？
Okay?
但是如果你像我一样在 CodePen 上构建它，
But if you're building it on CodePen like I'm going to do,
那么你将需要这张图片
then you will need this image
位于此 URL。
that is located at this URL.
所以我们只是从屏幕上复制到这里
So we just copy this here somehow from the screen
并将其用于您自己的项目。
and use it for your own project.
然后是图像的尺寸
Then the dimensions of the image
应该是 250 乘 250。
should be 250 by 250.
有了这个，我想我给了你一切
And with this, I think I gave you everything
你需要知道的。
that you need to know.
所以继续复制这个 URL
So go ahead and copy this URL
现在我将切换到默认页面视图
and now I will switch to default page view
这样您就可以立即看到所有内容
so that you can see everything at once
现在我就让你去做吧
and now I will just leave you to it
5 或 10 分钟后回到这里
and come back here in 5 or 10 minutes
一旦你准备好了。
once you are ready.
好的，我们回来了
Okay, here we are back
我希望这对你来说不是太大的挑战
and I hope that it wasn't too much of a challenge for you
这样我就不会太难了。
so that I wasn't too hard.
所以希望你得到
So hopefully you got
多练习一点技巧
to practice your skills a little bit more
所以现在如果你有任何疑问
and so now in case you have any doubts
或者你遇到任何问题，
or you run into any problem,
我现在将在这里向您展示我的解决方案。
I will now show you my solution here.
正如我提到的，我们在这里使用了一篇文章
So as I mentioned, we are using an article here
现在是标题，
and now for the heading,
我用的是h2，实际上不是h1
I used an h2, actually not an h1
因为这是一个组件的想法
because of that idea of this being a component
在更大的页面内。
within a bigger page.
所以每个页面应该只有一个 h1
And so each page should only have one h1
所以如果我们有 mul文章，
and so if we then have multiple articles,
那么他们每个人都应该只是一个h2。
then each of them should just be an h2.
匡威 Chuck Taylor 全明星。
Converse Chuck Taylor All Star.
好吧，我本可以从演示中复制它。
Well, I could have just copied this from the demo.
但无论如何。
But anyway.
所以我
So img
现在我真的会继续
and now I will actually go ahead
并在此处复制此 URL
and copy this URL here
在编辑器视图中。
in the editor view.
好的。
Okay.
然后替代文本是，
Then the alt text is,
我现在只是在这里复制它。
I'm just copying it now here.
这样应该就够了。
This should be enough like this.
然后是高度
And then the height
宽度为 250。
and the width at 250.
就在这里。
And here it is.
这是我们的形象。
Here is our image.
伟大的。
Great.
现在让我们回到这里
Now let's go back here
并实际复制所有这些内容。
and actually copy all of this content.
为什么不？
Why not?
然后我们就可以，在那之后，
Then we can just, after that,
将所有内容包装到自己的元素中。
wrap everything into its own element.
所以这里我们有价格。
So here we have the price.
我将继续为每个段落使用一个段落
And I will keep using a paragraph for each
这些元素中，
of these elements,
所以对于每个文本元素。
so for each of the text elements.
然后我们有免费送货。
00:11:39,130​​ --> 00:11:40,310
好的。
Then we have free shipping.
Okay.
你看到那个 CodePen
And you see that CodePen
实际上在那里自动做了一些缩进。
actually automatically did some indentation there.
所以这很有帮助。
So that's quite helpful.
然后这里还有一段。
Then here there's another paragraph.
对。
Right.
所以我们正在格式化我们的内容，
So we are getting our content formatted,
当然，除了所有内容
except, of course, for all the content
那不在任何元素内。
that is not inside any element.
所以请记住我是如何提到 HTML 无关紧要的
So remember how I mentioned that HTML doesn't care
关于任何间距或任何输入。
about any spacing or about any enters.
所以就像换行符。
So like line breaks.
一切都在同一条线上
Everything is just in the same line
这就是为什么我们需要构建我们的内容
and so that's why we need to structure our content
以合乎逻辑的方式。
in a logical way.
现在，这里我们有了那个锚元素。
Now, here we have that anchor element.
事实上，我并没有真正告诉你
And actually, I didn't really tell you
此链接应指向的位置。
where this link should point to.
所以你可以创建一个空链接
So you could have just created an empty link
基本上是这样的，
like this basically,
或者你可以链接匡威网站。
or you could have linked the Converse website.
所以让我抓住那个链接。
So let me just grab that link.
所以 converse.com 可能
So converse.com probably
我正在这样做。
and I'm doing it like this.
你马上就会明白为什么。
You will see in a moment why.
原因是因为我们实际上需要这个 https://。
And the reason is because we actually need this https://.
所以整个网址。
So the entire URL.
这不是必需的。
This is not necessary here.
现在让我们结束这个。
And now here let's close this.
当然，在这里，我们不只是想要这个符号
And here, of course, we do not just want this symbol
因为这并不完全正确，
because this is not really correct,
所以相反，我们想要那个 HTML 实体
so instead, we want that HTML entity
你希望使用。
that you hopefully used.
这就是右箭头。
So that is the right arrow.
所以这是这里的缩写，
So this is the abbreviation here,
for r 代表右
for r stands for right
然后 arr 为箭头
and then arr for arrow
确实，这就是我们得到的结果。
and so indeed, this is the result that we got.
好的。
Okay.
所以我们拥有所有这部分。
So we have all of this part.
现在让我们在这里处理这个列表
Now let's take care of this list here
和这个标题。
and this heading.
最后还有这个按钮。
And finally then also this button.
所以我这里已经有一个h2了，对吧？
So I have an h2 already up here, right?
所以对于这个，我现在使用的是 h3。
And so for this one, I'm using an h3 now.
H3。
H3.
并关闭它。
And closing it.
好的。
Nice.
现在记住，
And now remember,
为了创建一个列表，这就是我们想要的，
in order to create a list, which is what we want here,
所以一个项目符号列表，
so a bullet-pointed list,
我们使用无序元素
we use the unordered element
或者实际上，无序列表元素。
or actually, the unordered list element.
现在我们把所有的
And now we just wrap all
这些合为一个 li 元素，对吧？
of these into one li element, right?
所以我希望在这一点上，
So I hope that at this point,
你已经知道这些元素了。
you already know these elements.
所以你练习了很多
So you have practiced a lot
所以我确定
and so I'm sure
现在这对你来说变得容易多了。
that this is getting a lot more easy for you now.
让我们在这里删除这个点
Let's just remove this dot here
我们几乎完成了。
and we are almost done.
所以我们现在只需要最后那个按钮。
So all we need now is that button in the end.
正如我之前向你展示的那样，
And so as I showed you before,
为此，我们可以简单地使用 HTML 中的按钮元素。
for that, we can simply use the button element in HTML.
所以加入购物车。
So add to cart.
当然，那个按钮，
And of course, that button,
所以点击那个按钮不会做任何事情。
so clicking that button will not do anything.
为此，我们需要一些 JavaScript。
For that, we would need some JavaScript.
但至少它在这里是可见的，好吗？
But at least it is here visible, okay?
我们在这里看到我们有 80 个未保存的更改。
And we see here that we have 80 unsaved changes.
因此，如果您想再次保留这些更改，
So if you want to preserve those changes again,
你必须保存 CodePen
you would have to save the CodePen
并为此创建一个免费帐户。
and create a free account in order to do that.
哦，我以为我们真的完成了
Oh and I thought that we were actually done
带着这个挑战
with this challenge
但少了一小块。
but there is one small piece missing.
所以原文中的这段文字实际上是粗体的。
So this text here in the original is actually bold.
所以这是唯一的区别。
So that's the only difference.
所以这是我们缺少的东西。
So that's something that we're missing.
所以让我们简单地把这个值包装在这里，
And so let's simply wrap this value here,
所以这一切都变成了强烈的文字元素。
so all this text into a strong element.
不是弦，强。
Not string, strong.
你现在看到了，
And you see now at this point,
我们没有关闭这个标签，
we didn't close this tag,
所以这个强大的元素
so this strong element
所以现在剩下的
and so now all the rest
内容基本变强。
of the content basically became strong.
所以现在一切都很大胆
So everything is bold now
因为这个元素永远不会结束。
because this element never ends.
但是，当然，那将是一个错误。
But, of course, that would be a mistake.
它甚至不是有效的 HTML
It wouldn't even be valid HTML
但浏览器仍然不知何故
but the browsers somehow still
能够以某种方式呈现它。
are able to render it somehow.
但不管怎样，有了这个，我们完成了这个挑战
But anyway, with this, we finished this challenge
实际上还有 HTML 部分的介绍。
and actually also the introduction to HTML section.
所以一定要检查一切
So make sure to review everything
你刚刚在本节中学到的，
that you just learned in the section,
你所有的新技能，然后一旦你准备好了，
all your new skills and then once you are ready,
我们可以一起进入下一部分，
we can together move on to our next section,
这将是 CSS 的基础。
which will be the fundamentals of CSS.
所以你最终会学到
And so there you will finally learn
如何实际设置您的内容的样式
how to actually style your content
让它看起来更精致一点
and make it look a little bit more polished
而且更漂亮。
and more beautiful.
所以这真的非常令人兴奋
So that's really, really exciting
所以是的，一旦你准备好了，让我们继续前进。
and so yeah, once you're ready, let's move on there.
再见。
See you soon.